<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Olmaredo Stego</string>
    <string name="decodebt">Decode</string>
    <string name="photo">Photo</string>
    <string name="encodePick">Enter the message you want to hide or </string>
    <string name="pickFile">Open File</string>
    <string name="intensity">Set intensity of embedding.\nThe higher you choose, the worse it will be.</string>
    <string name="encode">Encode</string>
    <string name="select">Select image</string>
    <string name="hint">Input message here or -></string>
    <string name="info">This app lets you to hide a message in an image in order to communicate secretly.\n
        The steganographic process needs a signature derived from the autocorrelation matrix
        of the original image, like a sort of key. You can clip it after the encoding process and share it
        with your partner that will insert it into the field in the decoding tab along side the image
        carrying the message. A generic signature can be used but can\'t guarantee the performance of the
        original one. \n
        In the setting tab can be specified the block dimension, the bigger, the harder to detect the information, since the
        spectrum is larger and the key is longer. But with bigger blocks the image can hold less of them, so less information can be
        included. The image height parameter sets the height dimension of the output image, bigger images can hold more information,
        but the computation can take much longer and devices with no much RAM could have problems. To give you an idea, with default
        settings the maximum length of the message is around 600 characters.\n
        The algorithm is based on spread-spectrum steganography, more specifically on the optimal version defined by
        Gkizeli, Pados and Medley that maximizes the signal-to-interference-plus-noise ratio.
    </string>

    <string name="selectimagehides">Select the image that hide the message.</string>
    <string name="selectwichsignature">Enter the signature you want ot use.\nThe default signature is generic and suitable for all kind of natural image, but you can use a more specific one.</string>

    <string name="clipboard">Copy Signature</string>
    <string name="clipboardText">Copy Message</string>

    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="calorOnOff">Color</string>
    <string name="colorDescription">Choose whenever or not encode images in color</string>
    <string name="enterMessage">Enter the message you want to hide.\nYou can write it here:</string>
    <string name="radioOriginal">Original</string>
    <string name="radioStandard">Generic</string>
    <string name="hintSignture">Insert signature</string>
    <string name="px4">4 pixel</string>
    <string name="px8">8 pixel</string>
    <string name="px16">16 pixel</string>
    <string name="buttonSaveSetting">Save settings</string>
    <string name="heightImage">Define the height of the image once it has been cropped."</string>
    <string name="heightImageBig">Image height</string>
    <string name="blockSetting">Define the dimension in pixel of the block used in the steganographic method.</string>
    <string name="blockSettingBig">Block dimension</string>
    <string name="encSelect">Select the image.\nYou can choose an existing file or make a new photograph.</string>
    <string name="encSelectBig">Image</string>
    <string name="encMessageBig">Message</string>
    <string name="encOpenFile">... or open a text file</string>
    <string name="encIntensity">Intensity</string>
    <string name="encPercentage">0%</string>
    <string name="decSignatureBig">Signature</string>
    <string name="decSelect">Select image</string>
    <string name="decSelectBig">Image</string>
    <string name="paste">Paste key</string>

</resources>
